♪Come closer♪
اقترب ♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪ كن أكثر حميمية
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪ قل لي إن كنت أغوى
♪The moment you and I looked at each other♪
♪ في اللحظة التي نظرت فيها أنا وأنت إلى بعضنا البعض
♪We were both tempted♪
كلانا أغوى
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪ تذكر كم كنت خجولًا ♪
♪That day♪
♪ ذلك اليوم ♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪ ذكريات حلوة ♪
♪Please be more♪
♪ من فضلك كن اكثر
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪ كم أنا محظوظ لوجودك ♪
♪So sweet♪
♪ حلوة جدا ♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
= مساعدي المشاغب =
=Episode 8=
= الحلقة 8 =
Am I wrong?
هل انا مخطئ
You yelled at me?
صرخت في وجهي؟
What gives you the right?
ما يمنحك الحق؟
What's the point of jobs like this?
ما الهدف من وظائف مثل هذه؟
Right.
الصحيح.
You always stand high
أنت دائما تقف عاليا
and lean over to pity me.
واتكئ على الشفقة علي.
Have you asked me what I want?
هل سألتني ماذا أريد؟
Have you considered how that might make me feel?
هل فكرت كيف يمكن أن يجعلني ذلك أشعر؟
I'm not as dazzling as you,
أنا لست مبهرًا مثلك ،
but I cherish every opportunity.
لكني أعتز بكل فرصة.
Let's go back and talk about it.
دعنا نعود ونتحدث عنها.
I won't go back.
لن أعود.
I'm working.
أنا أعمل.
Zhang Duoduo!
تشانغ ديودو!
Are you feeling hot, sir?
هل تشعر بالحر يا سيدي؟
The next line is this.
السطر التالي هو هذا.
I'll fan for you.
سأعجب بك.
Bring the air conditioner here.
أحضر مكيف الهواء هنا.
(What? No way!)
(ماذا؟ لا مفر!)
(I will never work)
(لن اعمل ابدا)
(with unprofessional actors again.)
(مع الجهات الفاعلة غير المهنية مرة أخرى.)
(I didn't do anything wrong.)
(لم أفعل شيئًا خاطئًا.)
(Forget it.)
(انسى ذلك.)
Linda.
ليندا.
Help me with my schedule in Beijing.
ساعدني في تحديد الجدول الزمني الخاص بي في بكين.
Xing Enchen!
Xing Enchen!
Mr. Xing.
السيد شينغ.
Get in the car, please.
اركب السيارة من فضلك.
So handsome! Xing Enchen!
وسيم جدا! Xing Enchen!
Xing Enchen!
Xing Enchen!
(He never confessed love to me.)
(لم يعترف لي أبدًا بالحب).
(He never said he liked me.)
(لم يقل أبدًا أنه معجب بي).
(I might just be)
(قد أكون فقط)
(an obedient and funny doll to him.)
(دمية مطيعة ومضحكة له.)
(Zhang Duoduo!)
(تشانغ Duoduo!)
(Come on!)
(هيا!)
(It's better to leave than to stay here.)
(من الأفضل المغادرة بدلاً من البقاء هنا).
(Better than being heartbroken)
(أفضل من الحزن)
(every time I see him.)
(في كل مرة أراه.)
Duoduo.
ديودو.
Helen cheated on me.
لقد خدعتني هيلين.
He played games with that girl and then had sex with her.
لعب مع تلك الفتاة ثم مارس الجنس معها.
Jerks.
الحمقى.
Shame on you!
حرج عليك!
Zhang Duoduo!
تشانغ ديودو!
(Hand over your charge of my contract and the rest of the job to Linda.)
(سلم مسئوليتك عن عقدي وبقية المهمة إلى ليندا.)
(Okay.)
(تمام.)
My boyfriend slept with another girl.
لقد نام صديقي مع فتاة أخرى.
You don't even want to comfort me?
أنت لا تريد حتى أن تريحني؟
Are you still my bestie?
هل مازلت صديقي المفضل؟
Oh, my baby!
اوه عزيزي!
How pretty you are.
كم هي جميلة أنت.
Buddies will hope you continue to be together,
سيأمل الأصدقاء أن تظلوا معًا ،
while besties will hope you break up.
في حين أن أفضل الأصدقاء يأملون في الانفصال.
What's more, he's obviously a jerk.
ما هو أكثر من ذلك ، من الواضح أنه أحمق.
Break up with him,
انفصل عنه،
and ask him to return all the gifts you gave him.
واطلب منه أن يعيد كل الهدايا التي قدمتها له.
Stop saying that.
توقف عن قول ذلك.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I got a thing to handle.
لدي شيء لأتعامل معه.
I've gotta go out.
يجب أن أخرج.
There's food in the fridge.
هناك طعام في الثلاجة.
I'll be back soon.
سأعود قريبا.
(Duoduo.)
(Duoduo.)
(Do you confirm that the contract with Mr. Xing is okay?)
(هل تؤكد أن العقد مع السيد Xing على ما يرام؟)
(And)
(و)
(you won't be in charge of Mr. Xing's schedule anymore.)
(لن تكون مسؤولاً عن جدول السيد Xing بعد الآن.)
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪ إنه لأمر مؤسف
♪That we are not together in this life♪
بأننا لسنا معًا في هذه الحياة
♪But still, thank you♪
♪ لكن مع ذلك ، شكرًا لك ♪
♪For letting me♪
♪ لسماحك لي ♪
♪Walk into your world♪
♪ امش في عالمك ♪